{
  "level": 5,
  "unit": 2,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "The pain is in my elbow __________ .", "answer": "joint" },
        { "prompt": "A __________ smell filled the room.", "answer": "foul" },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ the rope so nobody will trip.",
          "answer": "coil"
        },
        { "prompt": "Just __________ the basket over.", "answer": "hoist" },
        { "prompt": "She was a __________ woman.", "answer": "stout" },
        { "prompt": "Let's not __________ along the way.", "answer": "dawdle" },
        { "prompt": "He chewed a __________ of food.", "answer": "mouthful" },
        {
          "prompt": "They ordered ice cream at the __________ .",
          "answer": "counter"
        },
        { "prompt": "The mailman __________ letters.", "answer": "brought" },
        { "prompt": "The baby started to __________ .", "answer": "bawl" },
        {
          "prompt": "We got a drink at the __________ .",
          "answer": "fountain"
        },
        { "prompt": "The cat __________ in the doorway.", "answer": "sprawls" },
        { "prompt": "__________ your hands in water.", "answer": "douse" },
        {
          "prompt": "Check the __________ in the contract.",
          "answer": "clause"
        },
        { "prompt": "Grass __________ from the lawn.", "answer": "sprouts" },
        {
          "prompt": "It could be dangerous, so be __________ .",
          "answer": "cautious"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There was __________ in the streets.",
          "answer": "turmoil"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The __________ dog was always hungry.",
          "answer": "scrawny"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The house has a firm __________ .",
          "answer": "foundation"
        },
        { "prompt": "Emma lost her __________ ring.", "answer": "turquoise" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "__________ shake their tails.", "answer": "rattlers" },
        { "prompt": "Their __________ are powerful tools.", "answer": "fangs" },
        {
          "prompt": "I want to visit different __________.",
          "answer": "countries"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We give up certain __________ at school.",
          "answer": "liberties"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mashed __________ are my favorite.",
          "answer": "potatoes"
        },
        { "prompt": "We saw cowboys at the __________.", "answer": "rodeos" },
        {
          "prompt": "My parents pay __________ every year.",
          "answer": "taxes"
        },
        { "prompt": "Snakes are also __________.", "answer": "reptiles" },
        { "prompt": "Be aware of your __________.", "answer": "surroundings" },
        { "prompt": "Sandy has strong __________.", "answer": "beliefs" },
        { "prompt": "We faced a lot of __________.", "answer": "difficulties" },
        {
          "prompt": "I baked three __________ of cookies.",
          "answer": "batches"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Dancing is one of her best __________.",
          "answer": "abilities"
        },
        { "prompt": "__________ protect our eyes.", "answer": "lashes" },
        { "prompt": "A spy can have many __________.", "answer": "identities" },
        {
          "prompt": "Our win makes up for all our __________.",
          "answer": "losses"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Let's explore all the __________.",
          "answer": "possibilities"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The __________ in the tree were made by a woodpecker.",
          "answer": "notches"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "How many __________ are in a million?",
          "answer": "zeroes"
        },
        { "prompt": "Fish hide in the river's __________.", "answer": "eddies" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I like __________ in the park.", "answer": "jogging" },
        { "prompt": "Please fix the __________ faucet.", "answer": "dripping" },
        { "prompt": "Julie __________ the chapter.", "answer": "skimmed" },
        {
          "prompt": "I __________ the trophy for my team.",
          "answer": "accepted"
        },
        { "prompt": "The comedy show was __________.", "answer": "amusing" },
        { "prompt": "We began __________ into our seats.", "answer": "easing" },
        {
          "prompt": "He __________ saying mean things.",
          "answer": "regretted"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "His mom was __________ him to play with us.",
          "answer": "forbidding"
        },
        { "prompt": "He __________ to the dictionary.", "answer": "referred" },
        {
          "prompt": "The __________ player needs surgery.",
          "answer": "injured"
        },
        { "prompt": "The team __________ to win.", "answer": "deserved" },
        { "prompt": "We __________ for a scholarship.", "answer": "applied" },
        { "prompt": "She __________ on their help.", "answer": "relied" },
        {
          "prompt": "I'm __________ the book for a week.",
          "answer": "renewing"
        },
        { "prompt": "This machine is __________.", "answer": "complicated" },
        { "prompt": "Maya is __________ for the job.", "answer": "qualified" },
        {
          "prompt": "That squirrel gave me a __________ look.",
          "answer": "threatening"
        },
        { "prompt": "We sat under a __________ tree.", "answer": "gnarled" },
        { "prompt": "The class __________ her talent.", "answer": "envied" },
        { "prompt": "The stars __________ him.", "answer": "fascinated" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I know __________ eaten already.", "answer": "you've" },
        {
          "prompt": "I think __________ like to go with us.",
          "answer": "she'd"
        },
        { "prompt": "__________ a beautiful sweater!", "answer": "that's" },
        { "prompt": "__________ your middle name?", "answer": "what's" },
        { "prompt": "He __________ like to swim.", "answer": "doesn't" },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ a large boat in the lake.",
          "answer": "there's"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ going to like that present.",
          "answer": "you're"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I __________ sure if I should leave.",
          "answer": "wasn't"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I think __________ have a sandwich for lunch.",
          "answer": "we'll"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ never been late for recess.",
          "answer": "we've"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ going on a fun field trip.",
          "answer": "we're"
        },
        { "prompt": "I __________ open that jar.", "answer": "couldn't" },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ been wanting to go to a movie.",
          "answer": "I've"
        },
        { "prompt": "We __________ like that last movie.", "answer": "didn't" },
        {
          "prompt": "__________ playing soccer tomorrow.",
          "answer": "they're"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We __________ be late for school.",
          "answer": "shouldn't"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I __________ like pickles in my soup.",
          "answer": "wouldn't"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I know __________ rather not play today.",
          "answer": "he'd"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We __________ need to throw that away.",
          "answer": "don't"
        },
        { "prompt": "Mrs. Sanchez __________ sick today", "answer": "isn't" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "The __________ examined Lisa's teeth.",
          "answer": "dentist"
        },
        { "prompt": "A __________ ran through the park.", "answer": "jogger" },
        { "prompt": "Joe turns __________ on Tuesday.", "answer": "fifteen" },
        { "prompt": "__________ her with compliments.", "answer": "flatter" },
        {
          "prompt": "Please __________ the library card application on Monday.",
          "answer": "submit"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Bob could tell the horse was a __________ .",
          "answer": "mustang"
        },
        { "prompt": "Kate was __________ from school.", "answer": "absent" },
        {
          "prompt": "The owl made a home in the __________ tree.",
          "answer": "hollow"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The __________ fell after the attack.",
          "answer": "empire"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The lights failed during the __________ .",
          "answer": "blizzard"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Each __________ has its own traditions.",
          "answer": "culture"
        },
        { "prompt": "He wore __________ to swim.", "answer": "goggles" },
        { "prompt": "He yelled to __________ the horse.", "answer": "summon" },
        { "prompt": "The game will __________ me.", "answer": "excite" },
        { "prompt": "The dog stayed at the __________ .", "answer": "kennel" },
        {
          "prompt": "A river curled through the __________ .",
          "answer": "valley"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I swept up the __________ of broken glass.",
          "answer": "fragment"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The horse took off at a __________ .",
          "answer": "gallop"
        },
        { "prompt": "The __________ circled its prey.", "answer": "vulture" },
        {
          "prompt": "The painter mixed __________ into the paint.",
          "answer": "pigment"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
